<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AI & Telecom News Digest</title>
    <link>https://ssikila.github.io/newsRSS_to_startme_page/</link>
    <description>Daily AI & Telecom insights curated by n8n + Perplexity</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telecom companies must adopt generative AI to reduce costs, drive growth, improve security, and transform into tech-focused automators offering AI-driven services.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[GenAI adoption in telecoms accelerates, reaching nearly 300 implementations by November 2024, reports STL Partners.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Microsoft's upcoming Telco industry data model in Microsoft Fabric, launching April 2025, aims to accelerate telecom innovation and growth through Cloud and AI adoption.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[AWS has chosen 40 startups for its 2025 Generative AI Accelerator, providing up to $1 million in AWS credits and expert support.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The telecom industry is rapidly adopting generative AI, with half of surveyed companies having implemented initial AI solutions by 2025.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The article highlights 150 AI use cases from startups, featuring Cursor, an AI-powered code editor with advanced generative AI and autonomous agent capabilities.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Deloitte's 2025 telecom outlook highlights generative AI as a key growth driver, with telcos exploring opportunities to capitalize on its expanding impact.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Generative AI, combined with AI-native platforms, zero trust, and quantum encryption, is driving the next growth wave in telecom enterprise security.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[EY warns the telecom sector faces increasing risks from AI challenges, ineffective transformations, and a complex geopolitical landscape.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[A new report reveals 83% of telecom leaders fear falling behind and urges telcos to adopt Gen AI to achieve productivity gains desired by 63%.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The Richmond Fed questions whether current AI investments are replicating the 1990s telecom boom and bust, suggesting a potential AI bubble.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Singtel Enterprise plans to become an AI-first telco by advancing AI-driven network slicing, digital twins, and autonomous networks.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[NVIDIA's 2025 survey shows 84% of telecom companies leveraging AI to drive industry growth and innovation.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Malaysia launches Ryt Bank, its first AI-powered bank, while Google expands access to its Veo 3 AI video creation tools.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Agentic AI is poised to transform telecommunications by automating processes and significantly boosting operational efficiency across the industry.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telefónica highlights that major hyperscalers like AWS, Azure, and GCP are advancing public clouds by integrating generative AI, foundational models, and synthetic data technologies.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  </channel>
</rss>