<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AI & Telecom News Digest</title>
    <link>https://ssikila.github.io/newsRSS_to_startme_page/</link>
    <description>Daily AI & Telecom insights curated by n8n + Perplexity</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telecom companies must adopt generative AI to reduce costs, drive growth, enhance security, and transform into technology-driven firms offering automated, AI-powered services.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[AWS chose 40 startups for its 2025 Generative AI Accelerator, providing up to $1 million in credits and expert support.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[By 2025, half of telecom companies have adopted generative AI, signaling significant integration of AI technologies in the telecommunications industry.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The article highlights 150 AI use cases from startups, including Cursor, an AI-powered code editor featuring advanced generative AI and autonomous agents.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Deloitte Insights highlights telcos exploring opportunities to leverage generative AI as a key growth driver in the 2025 telecom industry landscape.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Singtel Enterprise aims to become an AI-first telco by advancing AI-driven network slicing, digital twins, and autonomous networks.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[EY warns the telecom sector faces increasing risks from AI challenges, ineffective digital transformation, and a complex geopolitical landscape.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The European Commission will reveal its new strategy on October 8 to accelerate AI adoption across multiple European sectors.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The Richmond Fed questions whether current AI investments mirror the 1990s telecom boom and bust, hinting at a potential AI bubble.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Generative AI, combined with AI-native platforms, zero trust, and quantum encryption, is driving the next growth wave in telecom enterprise security.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[PwC forecasts key AI trends and actionable strategies driving business transformation in 2025 and beyond.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[AT&T launched Geo Modeler, an advanced generative AI platform to enhance geographic data modeling in telecommunications.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[A global study of 100+ tier-1 telecom executives highlights the emerging opportunities and practical applications of generative AI in the telecom industry.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Malaysia launches Ryt Bank, its first AI-powered bank, while Google's Veo 3 AI video creation tools become widely available.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[NVIDIA's 2025 survey shows 84% of telecom companies are leveraging AI to drive industry growth and innovation.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telefónica highlights that major hyperscalers like AWS, Azure, and GCP are integrating generative AI, foundational models, and synthetic data to shape the future of public clouds.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[ZTE advances intelligent network solutions by integrating AI to enhance telecom infrastructure and services.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  </channel>
</rss>