<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AI & Telecom News Digest</title>
    <link>https://yourusername.github.io/ai-news/</link>
    <description>Daily AI & Telecom insights curated by N8N + Perplexity</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telecoms must adopt generative AI to reduce costs, drive growth, improve security, and transform into tech companies offering automated, AI-powered services.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley's Tech, Media & Telecom 2025 report highlights emerging generative AI trends shaping the future of technology, media, and telecom industries.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The telecom industry is rapidly adopting generative AI, with half of surveyed companies having already implemented their first AI solutions by 2025.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The article highlights 150 AI use cases from startups, featuring Cursor, an AI-powered code editor with advanced generative AI and autonomous agent capabilities.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Deloitte's 2025 telecom outlook highlights generative AI as a key growth driver, with telcos exploring ways to capitalize on its expanding opportunities.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Singtel Enterprise aims to become an AI-first telco by investing in AI technologies like network slicing, digital twins, and autonomous networks.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[EY warns the telecom sector faces increasing risks from AI adoption challenges, ineffective digital transformation, and a shifting geopolitical landscape.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Generative AI, combined with zero trust and quantum encryption, is driving a transformative growth wave in telecom enterprise security through AI-native platforms.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The Richmond Fed questions whether the current surge in AI investments resembles the 1990s telecom boom and impending bust.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[A new report reveals 83% of telco leaders fear falling behind and urges urgent adoption of Gen AI to achieve productivity gains desired by 63% of the industry.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Keysight Technologies will showcase its AI-enabled 6G and advanced wireless solutions at a technology event from October 8–11, 2025.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Malaysia launches Ryt Bank, its first AI-powered bank, while Google’s Veo 3 AI video creation tools become widely available, highlighting AI's transformative impact.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[ZTE advances smart network solutions by integrating AI with telecommunications to enhance intelligent connectivity and innovation.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[The European Commission will unveil a new strategy on October 8 to promote AI adoption across multiple European sectors.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[A global study of 100+ tier-1 telecom executives reveals significant opportunities and practical applications for generative AI in the telecom industry.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[Telefónica highlights the integration of generative AI, foundational models, and synthetic data by major public cloud providers AWS, Azure, and GCP as key future trends.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
    <link></link>
    <description><![CDATA[PwC's 2025 AI Business Predictions highlight key trends and strategies driving AI's impact on business transformation across industries.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  </channel>
</rss>